A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 September 26 (Box-folder 004:112)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 October 5 (Box-folder 004:113)
- John Snow to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 7 (Box-folder 004:114)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 7 (Box-folder 004:115)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 9 (Box-folder 004:116)
- Claude M. Spilman, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 15 (Box-folder 004:117)
- Harman Hawkins to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 november 17 (Box-folder 004:118)
- M. George Henry to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 17 (Box-folder 004:119)
- James Y. Perry, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 17 (Box-folder 004:120)
- John Warren Day to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 22 (Box-folder 004:121)
- Philip Wogaman to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 November 29 (Box-folder 004:122)
- Howard A. Reed to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 1 (Box-folder 004:123)
- Frank A. Lindhorst to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 5 (Box-folder 004:124)
- Lawrence K. Whitfield to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 8 (Box-folder 004:125)
- C. F. Midelfort to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 9 (Box-folder 004:126)
- Paul Elmen to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 11 (Box-folder 004:127)
- Dewane Zimmerman to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 11 (Box-folder 004:128)
- Ted S. [C. K. S.] to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 13 (Box-folder 004:129)
- Latelle M. La Follette to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 21 (Box-folder 004:130)
- Huston Smith to Joseph Fletcher (et al), 1961 December 27 (Box-folder 004:131)
- William Howard Melish to Joseph Fletcher, 1961 December 28 (Box-folder 004:132)
- [Francis] Caswell to [Joseph Fletcher], [1961] (Box-folder 004:133)
- Bob [Geniesse] to Joseph Fletcher and family, [1961] (Box-folder 004:134)
- Correspondence of Bob Hall with Joseph Fletcher, ca. 1961 (Box-folder 004:135)
- Alfred T. Hamilton to Joseph Fletcher, [1961] (Box-folder 004:136)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 January 4 (Box-folder 005:001)
- earl C. Dahlstrom to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 January 23 (Box-folder 005:002)
- Cornelia Haines to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 January 23 (Box-folder 005:003)
- Telly(?) to Joseph Fletcher, [1962] January 30 (Box-folder 005:004)
- Alden Eberly to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 January 31 (Box-folder 005:005)
- John to Forrest and Joseph Fletcher, 1962 January 31 (Box-folder 005:006)
- Jessie Ruth Knowles to [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher], 1962 February 13 (Box-folder 005:007)
- Harvey Guthrie to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 Febriaru 16 (Box-folder 005:008)
- Jack [John Warren Day] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 February 19 (Box-folder 005:009)
- Patrick D. Wall to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 February 19 (Box-folder 005:010)
- Ship [Guy Emery Shipler] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 February 20 (Box-folder 005:011)
- W. Russell Bowie to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 1 (Box-folder 005:012)
- A. L. Kershaw to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 1 (Box-folder 005:013)
- Anson Phelps Stokes, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 1 (Box-folder 005:014)
- John C. Harper to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 12 (Box-folder 005:015)
- Edward T. Dell, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 16 (Box-folder 005:016)
- James L. Adams to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 20 (Box-folder 005:017)
- B. F. Skafran (?) to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 20 (Box-folder 005:018)
- Frederick P. Woodruff to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 20 (Box-folder 005:019)
- Maurice B. Rechitt (?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 March 21 (Box-folder 005:020)
- Rudolph Roell to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 23 (Box-folder 005:021)
- James F. Hoyle to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 March 26 (Box-folder 005:022)
- C. F. Midelfort to James A. Knight, [see 1962 May 3, 4 for meeting minutes (005:029) 1962 March 28 (Box-folder 005:023)
- Fra to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 April 2 (Box-folder 005:024)
- Wadi' Z. Haddad to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 April 11 (Box-folder 005:025)
- Eleanor G. Romig to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 April 17 (Box-folder 005:026)
- Guy Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 April 25 (Box-folder 005:027)
- Charlie F. D. Moule to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 April 27 (Box-folder 005:028)
- Meeting Minutes, Department of Pastoral Services, Commission of Religion and Health, Indianapolis, Indiana, [see 1962 March 28 for related letter (005: 023), 1962 May 3, 4 (Box-folder 005:029)
- Willard Uphaus to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 May 7 (Box-folder 005:030)
- Louis W. Hodges to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 10 (Box-folder 005:031)
- Lillie Mae Rose to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 11 (Box-folder 005:032)
- John B. Coburn to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 12 (Box-folder 005:033)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 15 (Box-folder 005:034)
- [Jane Fletcher] Geniesse to [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], 1962 May 19 (Box-folder 005:035)
- [Jane Fletcher] Geniesse to [Joseph Fletcher, Jr.?] 1962 May 22 (Box-folder 005:036)
- Everett Kleinjans to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 26 (Box-folder 005:037)
- W. C. Elliott to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1962 May 28 (Box-folder 005:038)
- F. [Forrest Fletcher] to Joe and Joe [Joseph Fletcher and Joseph, Jr.], 1962 May 29 (Box-folder 005:039)
- Lichty [Arthur Lichtenberger] to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 May 29 (Box-folder 005:040)
- F [Forrest Fletcher] to Joe and Joe [Joseph Fletcher and Joseph, Jr.], 1962 May 31 (Box-folder 005:041)
- M. [Forrest Fletcher] to Joe and Joe [Joseph Fletcher and Joseph, Jr.], 1962 May (Box-folder 005:042)
- Paul Ramsey to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 June 1 (Box-folder 005:043)
- Maurice B. Rechitt (?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 June 1 (Box-folder 005:044)
- F. [Forrest Fletcher] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 June 5 (Box-folder 005:045)
- F. [Forrest Fletcher] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 June 7 (Box-folder 005:046)
- John Lamont to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 June 7 (Box-folder 005:047)
- Charlie to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 June 9 (Box-folder 005:048)
- May A. Mason to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 June 12 (Box-folder 005:049)
- Chad Walsh to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1962] June 14 (Box-folder 005:050)
- Marion K. Snaders to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 June 27 (Box-folder 005:051)
- J. [Jane Fletcher Geniesse] to [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher and Joseph, Jr.?], [1962 June] (Box-folder 005:052)
- John G. Harrell to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 July 3 (Box-folder 005:053)
- Roland Gammon to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 July 16 (Box-folder 005:054)
- Stanley to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 July 24 (Box-folder 005:055)
- Philip T. Zabriskie to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 August 7 (Box-folder 005:056)
- Bill [William B. Spofford] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 August 10 (Box-folder 005:057)
- Maurice B. Rechitt (?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 August 22 (Box-folder 005:058)
- F. W. Dillistone to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 August 24 (Box-folder 005:059)
- Chad [Walsh] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 August 25 (Box-folder 005:060)
- Special License granted to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 Aaugust 28 (Box-folder 005:061)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 4 (Box-folder 005:062)
- Edward O. Miller to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 5 (Box-folder 005:063)
- Jacob A. Viverette, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 14 (Box-folder 005:064)
- Archer Harman, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 18 (Box-folder 005:065)
- Ship [Guy Emery Shipler] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 September 20 (Box-folder 005:066)
- Henry G. Turnbull to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 21 (Box-folder 005:067)
- James G. Vermillion to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 September 25 (Box-folder 005:068)
- Albert J. Chafe to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 September 27 (Box-folder 005:069)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 1 (Box-folder 005:070)
- George Gray Zabriskie to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 4 (Box-folder 005:071)
- Clement Alexander to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 10 (Box-folder 005:072)
- John [Coburn] to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 15 (Box-folder 005:073)
- Henry Chadwick to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 16 (Box-folder 005:074)
- William A. Overholt to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 22 (Box-folder 005:075)
- John B. Tillson to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 26 (Box-folder 005:076)
- Memoranda and Notes Concerning a Faculty Position at Episcopal Theological School, 1962 October 26, 29, 30, 6 Items (Box-folder 005:077)
- Pauline B. Taylor to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 October 29 (Box-folder 005:078)
- Dick to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 November 3 (Box-folder 005:079)
- Charlie F. D. Moule to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 November 12 (Box-folder 005:080)
- J. C. Michael Allen to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 November 13 (Box-folder 005:081)
- Arthur C. King to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 November 13 (Box-folder 005:082)
- John M. Musser to [Joseph] Fletcher, 1962 November 15 (Box-folder 005:083)
- John B. Morris to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 November 17 (Box-folder 005:084)
- J. Brooke Mosley to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 December 7 (Box-folder 005:085)
- Hazel Sagoff to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 December 11 (Box-folder 005:086)
- Robert J. Hadley to Joseph Fletcher, 1962 December 12 (Box-folder 005:087)
- Joseph Fletcher to Everett Kleinjans, 1962 December 17 (Box-folder 005:088)
- Robert B. Campbell to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, [1962] (Box-folder 005:089)
- [Jane Fletcher Geniesse] to [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher and Joseph, Jr.?], [1962] (Box-folder 005:090)
- William F. Gilroy to Joseph Fletcher, [1962] (Box-folder 005:091)
- Va. [Mrs. Linus E. Kittredge] to Joseph [Joseph Fletcher], 1962 (Box-folder 005:092)
- Wade Stinson to Joseph Fletcher, [1962] (Box-folder 005:093)
- Paul Bankston to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 January 15 (Box-folder 005:094)
- Emily [Kittredge?] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1963 January 15 (Box-folder 005:095)
- Harvey Guthrie to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 January 25 (Box-folder 005:096)
- Va. [Mrs. Linus E. Kittredge] to Joseph [Joseph Fletcher], [1963 January] (Box-folder 005:097)
- Va. [Mrs. Linus E. Kittredge] to Joseph [Joseph Fletcher], [1963 January] (Box-folder 005:098)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 4 (Box-folder 005:098)
- Jacques P. Bossiere to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 5 (Box-folder 005:099)
- Mary Louise Vincent to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 12 (Box-folder 005:100)
- Mary Louise Vincent to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 12 (Box-folder 005:100)
- Robert M. Russell to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 13 (Box-folder 005:101)
- George Easter to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1963 February 19 (Box-folder 005:102)
- Jim L. Adams to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 February 21 (Box-folder 005:103)
- Hette DeForest to [Joseph Fletcher], 1963 February 28 (Box-folder 005:104)
- Hazel Sagoff to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 March 5 (Box-folder 005:105)
- John [Coburn] to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 March 12 (Box-folder 005:106)
- Daniel L. Gibbes, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 March 14 (Box-folder 005:107)
- J. Brooke Mosley to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1963 march 23 (Box-folder 005:108)
- Hallam C. Shorrock, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 3 (Box-folder 005:109)
- Ada Allfort to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 4 (Box-folder 005:110)
- Lewis N. Lukens to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 10 (Box-folder 005:111)
- Don to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 26 (Box-folder 005:112)
- A[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 29 (Box-folder 005:113)
- Richard F. Hettlinger to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 April 30 (Box-folder 005:114)
- Howard Root to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 May 2 (Box-folder 005:1)
- Sam H. Franklin to Joseph Fletcher, 1963 November 14 (Box-folder 005:116)
- A Poem, [1963] (Box-folder 005:117)
- A Poem for John Coburn, [1963] (Box-folder 005:118)
- Luke Cheung to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 January 27 (Box-folder 006:001)
- Charles P. Gilson to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 February 5 (Box-folder 006:002)
- Masao Takenaka to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 February 6 (Box-folder 006:003)
- Herbert Brewer to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 March 24 (Box-folder 006:004)
- William Eddy to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 April 26 (Box-folder 006:005)
- Meeting Transcript: Joseph Fletcher and Hokkaido University Economics Professors, 1964 May 12 (Box-folder 006:006)
- Bill {William Eddy} to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 May 18 (Box-folder 006:007)
- Bob Smith to [Joseph Fletcher], 1964 May 22 (Box-folder 006:008)
- Alec N. Vidler(?) to Joseph [Joseph Fletcher], 1964 August 21 (Box-folder 006:009)
- Brian Richard Boylan to Joseph Fletcher, with notes by Joseph Fletcher, 1964 September 25 (Box-folder 006:010)
- Gordon Hubel to Y. Katahira, 1964 October 6 (Box-folder 006:011)
- Dana Copp to Joseph Fletcher, 1964 October 19 (Box-folder 006:012)
- Form letter concerning national observance of the Bill of Rights, 1964 December (Box-folder 006:013)
- Materials realted to the Association for Humane Abortion, 1964 December - 1965 March, 24 Items (Box-folder 006:014)
- Richard R. Niebuhr to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 January 5 (Box-folder 006:015)
- William Scarlett to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 January 12 (Box-folder 006:016)
- Minutes of the Board of Directors Meeting, Association for Humane Abortion, Inc., 1965 March 9 (Box-folder 006:017)
- Memorandum and Financial Report for the Board of Directors, Association for Humane Abortion, by Ruth Proskauer Smith, 1965 March 16 (Box-folder 006:018)
- J. to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1965?] March 21 (Box-folder 006:019)
- Ruth Proskauer Smith to Joseph Fletcher and isreal R. Margolies, 1965 April 7 (Box-folder 006:020)
- Kenneth W. Mann to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure 1965 April 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 006:021)
- Cyril C. Means to Ruth Proskauer Smith, 1965 April 18 (Box-folder 006:022)
- Cyril C. Means, Jr. to John De Jarnette Pemberton, Jr., 1965 April 21 (Box-folder 006:023)
- Materials concerning Jonathan Myrick Daniels, 1965 August 25, October, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 006:024)
- Cyril C. Means, Jr. to Elizabeth Ramsey, 1965 April 29 (Box-folder 006:025)
- David Burleson to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 April 30 (Box-folder 006:026)
- Ron Silverman to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 April 30 (Box-folder 006:027)
- Draft and final version of a letter for the Association for Human Abortion, Inc., Clergymen's Advisory Committee, by Joseph Fletcher and Isreal R. Margolies, 1965 April, 4 Items (Box-folder 006:028)
- Lenore Cahn to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 May 9 (Box-folder 006:029)
- Nathan M. Pusey to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 May 11 (Box-folder 006:030)
- Cyril C. Means, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 May 13 (Box-folder 006:031)
- Materials concerning birth control, 1965 May, 9 Items (Box-folder 006:032)
- Samuel H. Miller to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 June 4 (Box-folder 006:033)
- Materials concerning Episcopal Theological School student Jeremy G. Hole, 1965 June 4, 7 (Box-folder 006:034)
- Samuel H. Miller to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 June 7 (Box-folder 006:035)
- Jessica Reynolds to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1965 July 21 (Box-folder 006:036)
- Jessica Reynolds to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1965 August 6 (Box-folder 006:037)
- Will Hatch to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1965 August 9 (Box-folder 006:038)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 August 10 (Box-folder 006:039)
- Ninette H. Jeanty Raven to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 August 24 (Box-folder 006:040)
- Brief on medical issues from the Division of Pastoral Services of the Episcopal Diocese of Los Angeles, Kenneth W. Mann, chair, 1965 September 3 (Box-folder 006:041)
- Clipping from "Living Church," 1965 September 12 (Box-folder 006:042)
- John T. Noonan, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 September 17 (Box-folder 006:043)
- Lester Kinsolving to Mildred P. Smith, 1965 September 22 (Box-folder 006:044)
- E[ ] B. Sterner to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 October 1 (Box-folder 006:045)
- Memorial service bulletin for Donald A. Ramspell, with remarks by Joseph Fletcher, 1965 October 7 (Box-folder 006:046)
- Ruth Proskauer Smith to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 October 7 (Box-folder 006:047)
- John H. Knowles to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1965 October 22, 2 Items (Box-folder 006:048)
- Wedding service bulletin for Sylvia Josephine Wackenhut and Jeffrey Linus Kittredge, with notes for a sermon by Joseph Fletcher, 1965 October 30 (Box-folder 006:049)
- Ruth Proskauer Smith to Joseph Fletcher, enclosing a form letter from the Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. 1965 November 2 (Box-folder 006:050)
- Les [Lester Kinsolving] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1965 November 4 (Box-folder 006:051)
- Ship [Guy E. Shipler] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], forwarding a letter from William A. Sassman, 1965 November 4 (Box-folder 006:052)
- John V. Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 November 5 (Box-folder 006:053)
- Ian T. Ramsey to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 November 22 (Box-folder 006:054)
- Charlie F. D. Moule to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 November 26 (Box-folder 006:055)
- F. W. Dillistone to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 November 29 (Box-folder 006:056)
- E. Mollier Batten to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 November 30 (Box-folder 006:057)
- Lecture notice with note by John S[ ] to [Joseph Fletcher], 1965 November (Box-folder 006:058)
- Anthony de Marinis to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 December 2 (Box-folder 006:059)
- Jim Tuverson, Jr. and Bob Kennedy to Joseph Fletcher, 1965 December 17 (Box-folder 006:060)
- Promotional materials for books by Joseph Fletcher, 1965 December - 1968 July, N.D. (Box-folder 006:061)
- Incomplete memorandum from Sylvia Bloom for the Association for Humane Abortion, Inc., [1965] (Box-folder 006:062)
- John Giles Milhaven to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 3 (Box-folder 006:063)
- H. Paul Osborne to Alfred Pol Nicholas Ferdinand Stiernotte, with copy of letter from Stiernotte to the editor, The Register-Leader, 1966 January 8, 2 Items (Box-folder 006:064)
- Robert Kotlowitz to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 20 (Box-folder 006:065)
- L. V. N. Rusling to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 25 (Box-folder 006:066)
- Philip W. Van Vlack to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 25 (Box-folder 006:067)
- Pamela Lowry to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 26 (Box-folder 006:068)
- Jim Tuverson, Jr. and Bob Kennedy to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 26 (Box-folder 006:069)
- J. A. Schumacher to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 January 31 (Box-folder 006:070)
- Robert W. Barnett to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 1 (Box-folder 006:071)
- Clement Alexandre to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 4 (Box-folder 006:072)
- T. Edward Damer to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 6 (Box-folder 006:073)
- Philip M. Horan, Policy regarding faculty houses, Episcopal Theological School, 1966 February 8 (Box-folder 006:074)
- John B. Coburn to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 9 (Box-folder 006:075)
- Jan J. Erteszek to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 9 (Box-folder 006:076)
- Richard J. Trudeau to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 13 (Box-folder 006:013)
- Planned Parenthood Newsletter, 1966 February 15 (Box-folder 006:078)
- Jewell Peterson Hunter to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], with a memorandum by Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 19, 25 (Box-folder 006:079)
- Paul Swain Havens to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 26 (Box-folder 006:080)
- Jerry to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 February 28 (Box-folder 006:081)
- Anne and Paul Van Buren to Forrest and Joe [Forrest and Joseph Fletcher], 1966 March 1 (Box-folder 006:082)
- Peter Davison to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 2 (Box-folder 006:083)
- Wilfren Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 18 (Box-folder 006:084)
- Brooklyn college Philosophy Examination, 1966 Spring (Box-folder 006:085)
- A. Benjamin Downing to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 26 (Box-folder 006:086)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 26 (Box-folder 006:087)
- Theodore Fritsch to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 29 (Box-folder 006:088)
- Robert A. Burch to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 March 30 (Box-folder 006:089)
- Gordon to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1966] April 4 (Box-folder 006:090)
- Ed to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 April 7 (Box-folder 006:091)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 April 11 (Box-folder 006:092)
- Elizabeth Larsson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 April 13 (Box-folder 006:093)
- H. H. Hutchinson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 April 14 (Box-folder 006:094)
- Lael Wertenbaker to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 April 17 (Box-folder 006:095)
- Maeve to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 April 22 (Box-folder 006:096)
- Lulu Chewning to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1966 April 25 (Box-folder 006:097)
- Birth announcement from Jean and Chuch Lange, 1966 April 26 (Box-folder 006:098)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 April 29 (Box-folder 006:099)
- David Van Meter to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 2 (Box-folder 006:100)
- Norman Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 4 (Box-folder 006:101)
- Wylfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 5 (Box-folder 006:102)
- Frank W. Hogan to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 14 (Box-folder 006:103)
- Robert T. Mason to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 17 (Box-folder 006:104)
- Joseph Fletcher to Fred D. Cunningham, with response by Cunningham to Fletcher, 1966 May 18 (Box-folder 006:105)
- J. D. Jago to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 18 (Box-folder 006:106)
- Harvey D. Frank to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 20 (Box-folder 006:107)
- Ed Harvey to [Joseph Fletcher], [1966 May 20] (Box-folder 006:108)
- Richard D. Tyree to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 24 (Box-folder 006:109)
- Richard Byfield to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 25 (Box-folder 006:110)
- C. Paulette Easter to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 27 (Box-folder 006:111)
- Owaldi(?) to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 May 27 (Box-folder 006:112)
- Paul L. Meacham to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 1 (Box-folder 007:001)
- Richard D. Tyree to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 2 (Box-folder 007:002)
- Jock Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 4 (Box-folder 007:003)
- Robert E. Merry to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 7 (Box-folder 007:004)
- Arthur C. Dechene, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 9 (Box-folder 007:005)
- Joseph F. Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 9 (Box-folder 007:006)
- Dennid Griebenou to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 11 (Box-folder 007:007)
- Alfred W. Whitehurst to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 14 (Box-folder 007:008)
- Paul L. Lehmann to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 15 (Box-folder 007:009)
- Richard P. Unsworth to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 16 (Box-folder 007:010)
- Mary Theresa CSJ. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 18 (Box-folder 007:011)
- Donald Kalish to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 22 (Box-folder 007:012)
- C. Philip Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 June 27 (Box-folder 007:013)
- Harmon L. Smith to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 June 28 (Box-folder 007:014)
- Mary B. Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July (Box-folder 007:015)
- Paul Schlueter to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 2 (Box-folder 007:016)
- George K. Storm to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 9 (Box-folder 007:017)
- Ethel Shachtman to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 12 (Box-folder 007:018)
- Alfred E. Andrews to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 13 (Box-folder 007:019)
- Warren L. Howell to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 13 (Box-folder 007:020)
- Philip E. Wheaton to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 13 (Box-folder 007:021)
- Scott Paradise to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 14 (Box-folder 007:022)
- June S. Mather to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 July 18 (Box-folder 007:023)
- Donald E. Bitsberger to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 1 (Box-folder 007:024)
- Herman C. Ahrens, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 3 (Box-folder 007:025)
- George J. Hebert to Joseph Fletcher, with attached review of Situation Ethics, 1966 August 7 (Box-folder 007:026)
- Robert S. Lehman to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 10 (Box-folder 007:027)
- Mrs. Luen F. Jacobs to [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 (Box-folder 007:028)
- Rooney N. Usher-Wilson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 17 (Box-folder 007:029)
- Vernon Robertson to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 August 18 (Box-folder 007:030)
- Rustum Roy to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 29 (Box-folder 007:031)
- Durrett Wagner to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 August 29 (Box-folder 007:032)
- Nat Lehrmanto Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 1 (Box-folder 007:033)
- Eileen Paulto Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1966 September 6 (Box-folder 007:034)
- Robert C. Gardner to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 7 (Box-folder 007:035)
- Alfred M. Niese, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 8 (Box-folder 007:036)
- Colby Lewis to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 12 (Box-folder 007:037)